We'll be right back.
Spondum Ski, the day the sea train shook.
Interesting.
Many ships were born in this cobwebbed room.
And now look at it.
Filthy.
They built ships here?
Tom, Iceberg, and Cutty Flam.
This place must hold countless memories of days when you still shared a life with those two.
And now you call it your top secret base.
That's heartbreakingly adorable.
Damn you.
Just get the hell out of here already.
We won't leave till we get what we're after.
Make this easy on yourself.
There ain't no blueprints in here.
Oh, no?
You don't say.
Hey!
Califa!
Oh, damn it!
Just keep it together, Usopp!
You bastard!
Take your time, but be aware that we know many things about your past.
Things that you don't want getting out.
For example, we know what happened eight years ago.
And that you are guilty of committing a very serious crime back then.
Just like your dear old Tom.
You shut up!
Tom was never a damn criminal!
You don't know what the hell you're talking about!
You freak!
Tom!
Stay back!
I disagree.
You're both criminals.
And as such, you should be made to feel the consequences of your actions.
Frankie, whatever happens, don't interfere with what I'm about to do.
No matter what.
You talk like you know everything.
You don't know Tom.
And you don't know anything about Water 7!
I heard the judicial ship will be here in three days.
Finally putting Tom on trial, are they?
I hope it ends well for him.
I'm sure it will.
Right.
He fulfilled his promise, after all.
That he did.
All right, let's get that lumber in the dock.
So, how'd the deal work out with St. Poplar?
Not that great.
They're taking advantage of us since we don't have much to trade with them.
Like iron from San Valdo.
We'll all be in the red if this kind of crap keeps up.
We're not gonna let this keep happening now, are we guys?
Yeah!
No way!
The people do seem to be happy about being able to cross the ocean.
But they say the trade situation isn't as good as they'd hoped.
I wonder if this town needs more than a sea train.
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha!
Ah, but the spirits are up, boy!
That's a major step, so give the rest some time.
We've done our best, so be proud.
Keep your head held high and walk with gusto!
Let's go!
Yeah.
You there!
Am I correct in assuming I'm speaking with Mr. Tom, the shipbuilding engineer?
You're a difficult man to pin down.
Hmm?
I have some matter of great importance I wish to...
Um, sir?
This man and I are talking!
Yes, sir!
Again, before I was so rudely...
Hmm?
I was going to say, my name is Agent Spondum from Cypher Pole number five!
Stop it, sir!
Ha ha ha ha ha!
Wow!
Sorry about that!
My bad!
Looks like you got in the way of my victory cannon salute!
Tough luck!
It's super!
Battle Frankie 35 comes home with booty!
That's right!
Check it out!
Is this not the biggest sea king you ever laid your eyes on?
Ha ha ha ha!
I can't believe him.
I'm still acting like a child.
Hey!
What the hell do you think you're doing, ice for brains?
Oh!
Will you ever grow up?
Ever since you were a kid, all you want to do is build these stupid battleships.
It's time to stop.
This better be the last one, or I'm going to start tearing them all apart myself.
Want a vet? You lay a finger on my ship, and you'll draw back a stump, you hear me?
Yeah? Well, listen, Frankie, if you were able to kill a sea king with this floating piece of junk,
that means it's a dangerous weapon.
And you've got all those other battleships of yours just strewn around here?
What are you thinking?
Hey, it's not like I'm attacking people with them, am I?
I'm not saying you do that, but you're making it easier for anyone else who'd want to, you idiot.
Am I right? Back me up here, Tom.
Flunky's weapons are going to be the end of our business.
Flunky, that's rich.
Hold on, this is no laughing matter.
I demand a sincere apology and that you listen to what I've come here to say.
Government guy, are you? So, is this about the trial?
Trial? What the devil are you talking about?
No, this concerns an altogether different matter.
Oh, now what?
Did Tom come back with you boys?
No, I think he's with a visitor.
Some man from the government.
It wasn't about the trial.
Spawn, spawn something.
Spawn something dumb, maybe?
How strange.
And he's not from the judicial ship?
The government is so disorganized.
Afraid not. I've got no blueprints for something like that.
That's nonsense.
Do you take me for some kind of weak-minded simpleton?
I researched the history of Water 7 for countless hours.
And I am absolutely certain this document can only be in your possession.
You're saying that you actually have the authority to investigate me?
That's right, I do.
And what's more, I learned all about your dealings with Gold Roger in the course of my investigation.
So unless you want me to share that information with my colleagues, you're going to cooperate.
Why would I care? The government already knows about it.
We do?
That's such a poppycock.
If that's true, why are you here and not rotting away somewhere in a jail cell?
Use your investigative powers and find out for yourself.
Good day.
Hey, you can't treat a government agent like this.
Open this door immediately.
That's right.
It's all true.
Yes, sir.
He did exactly what he told the judge he'd do.
And they should be dropping the charges at the trial that's coming up.
That man saved this island for sure.
It makes my blood boil to think that damn criminal is being treated like a hero.
I see.
You're certain that such a thing truly exists?
Yes, sir.
And the pirates are scouring the globe for it as we speak.
That's why it's imperative we locate it immediately.
If it were to fall into the wrong hands, the resulting destruction would be inconceivable.
We've been suffering through this great pirate era for more than a decade now.
It's a vile sickness that grows worse with every passing day.
The time for idle discussion is over.
We must do more than to prevent this weapon's construction.
We must build it ourselves and use it as a mighty instrument of justice.
With it, we can eliminate this pirate scourge and bring law and order back to our land.
This is indeed a troubling error.
There's no doubt about that.
Your primary objective will be to locate and then obtain these blueprints.
That will be all at this time.
We trust that you can complete this mission, Spondum.
Yes, sir. Without fail.
I've been working on this case for far too long to see it all go up in smoke.
It's right within my grasp now.
Let's go.
If the judge decides to acquit him, that'll mean a real headache for me.
Spondum, sir!
The charge will stick, and that bastard will hang.
Men, I'll need five more agents, stat!
Hmm.
Spondum, sir!
Iceberg, Frankie.
Yeah?
Hey, boys, come here.
What's up?
It's about time I let you in on something important.
Hmm.
Why would anyone even dream of something like this?
Is this for real?
Can this thing actually be built?
Those are the blueprints for a nightmare.
A real monster.
The government has learned of their existence and has started sniffing around for them.
It's too dangerous for me to keep them anymore.
This is terrifying, but I agree.
I'll keep them.
Iceberg!
Hey, let's see if we can build this thing!
You idiot!
Ow!
Do you ever think before you speak, this thing can never be built?
Do you realize how much destruction it could cause?
Huh?
Hmm.
Yeah.
The world would be done for.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
Besides trying to build the damn thing, you can do whatever the hell you want with it for now.
Even toss it if you need to.
Yes, of course.
Well, I got your attention.
Here's another storm a-brewin'.
Frankie, hold on.
Ah.
For what?
For your pants, you silly boy.
I swear, you'd think after all that attention you got last time you went out dressed like that,
you'd be wise enough not to do it again.
Jeez, I'm just going out to get a few things.
Ha, ha, ha.
Now that you're dressed, you can skeedaddle.
Thanks.
Can't believe she's making a big dinner just because the stupid judge is finally saying Tom's not guilty.
Never was in the first place.
Ha, ha, ha.
All right.
Rise and shine!
Tom, iceberg, give up!
Today's judgment day.
Don't want to sleep through your big trial.
Let's get down to the harbor!
They're gonna hand down Tom's sentence!
The spectators are boarding the ship in droves.
The people are really interested.
Seems like it'll be a big trial.
Seems that way.
Have you had a chance to see the sea train yet, Your Honor?
Hmm.
I have indeed.
Quite impressive.
A true feat of ingenuity.
He fulfilled his end of the bargain.
I'm certain the people will rejoice to see their hero go free.
Is Tom here yet?
I wish I could start already.
Come on.
We gotta hurry before all the seats are taken.
I know.
I can't wait to see the look on his face when the judge lets him off.
What a trip.
Wow.
Can't believe it's been 14 years.
That ship's under attack!
Get away from it!
Hooray!
What the?
Is this a pirate raid?
But how?
Where is this attack even coming from?
Hey, look!
Over there!
What?
Some kind of fleet!
Those look like battleships.
Those pirates are attacking us!
There's so many of them!
Are they all working together?
Everybody, run!
Get out of the harbor!
Hurry!
It's not safe, they're the water!
My danger!
Break my danger!
What's happening?
Who the hell?
Who's doing this?
Who took my ships?
Tom!
We're in trouble!
Hmm?
Frankie's ships are attacking the harbor.
It's not him.
I saw him earlier.
He wouldn't do such a thing.
I know that!
Look, I'm positive it's not Frankie doing it.
This is a whole other kind of trouble we're in.
Let's put a stop to it.
Right!
Pirates.
Or worse, the government!
Be back the way!
Hurry!
Into the city!
Get away from the harbor!
The harbor's still inside!
Bastards!
They're gonna pay!
Who the hell is it?
Huh?
夢見た僕らは間違いじゃないと信じて 荒く埋める海原を渡って行ける
誰よりも勇敢で思いやりもあるけれど
もしも君がこの船を降りて 違う世界にいたとしても
最後にはきっと笑えるよ
えっと毎食居るに参考え coc была
Let the sea train cry! I'm gonna be king of the pirates!